23, we'll have the invocation, the director of the North Campus, North Campus Ministries, Mr.
Steve, what's up?
Thank you for the opportunity of being here, like the report that we're running around 200
kids, athletes in our weekly fillet ship, Christian athlete, Bible studies, and couldn't
be better.
Probably we thank you for this time that we can come and call on you, pray for Mayor Parker,
Manjuries, and our council members, as they make important decisions for our city.
We thank you for the freedom we have to come and pray to seek you asking for wisdom and
guidance in all that we do for our city, bless this meeting in Jesus' name of pray.
Amen.
I believe it's to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which
it says, one nation, under God, they give us a little liberty and justice for all.
From the four public input, our unscheduled personal appearances, by claims report.
Make a motion, my proof.
Hi.
How's your turn?
Six.
Proved the need of motion.
Proved the minutes of the September 18th, 2023.
Motion.
Take it.
Hi.
Eastern.
Parker.
Hi.
Seven.
David Syracchermaine Klein for Pensacola, GRDA Realizing Scene, an Associated Complaint,
Proceedings in the amount of 37,598 dollars and 60 cents.
May you remember in the Council in your packet, you have this claim for disbursements and current
from August 1st, 2023, for August 31st, 2023 and we have the city of Miami and focused on communication
between the Miami team and the current legal proceedings.
This is well within the budget.
The current balance for this budget item is $697,775.
If the current claim is approved that would leave us a balance of $659,419.
Happy to answer any questions.
I'm like a moustache to approve the payment.
Second.
Hi.
Parker.
Hey.
Budget amendment.
This is MSUA Fund Carrier Over and it cumbers metering L.
electric funds.
No, there.
So this amendment does increase the carry over as you know when we would have done the budget,
we would have done that.
So what this is the actual that we're going to be doing over, we'll increase the funds so
that we're able to spend for me during for the hand telemeters and for electric for a dump truck
and a service truck.
Any issues with supply?
Like that is.
And for it is that we're starting to get equipment in, of course, there's still a quite
bit of a lag.
So it's still very, very kind of more movement with that tool, you won't have to
be for having to carry over as a one-to-one.
Thank you.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Take.
So go ahead.
What use?
Okay.
E step back.
All right.
We're not in ratified renew the following annual contracts from fiscal year, 2324 items A through K.
So may I remember you to the council, the list that you have in the front of you or a list
of contracts that we are asking to go ahead and approve these contracts through the end of this
fiscal year.
Previously we had them on an agenda item and they were looped in and included in some that we were
putting a three month term on.
But these contracts have been previously competitively bid and approved for multi-year contracts.
And so these, rather than going out and renewing these contracts, which will absolutely
result in an increase, these contracts we want to see through the end of this fiscal year, since
that's what our budget was set on.
Now what this does do is exclude several contracts that council wanted us to pay closer attention
to and review, such as the Torres Concrete, the Neese Concrete, Scott Controxions, Construction,
and the Collins Construction.
Those contracts will continue to be reviewed by our construction subcommittee, as we're
looking at developing a standard operating procedure and developing a threshold by which we
may want to be bidding out some of those projects depending on what's most fiscal responsible.
So the subcommittee is continuing to review those other contracts, the contracts that are on
the list today are simply the ones that we're previously bid and have not been in any dispute.
The four that you pull out, where they're not previously bid also, they were previously
bid, but those are the ones that we want to really evaluate whether or not.
going out to bid project my project would result in a savings or if the contract price that we have would
result in greater savings. So
We won't run the risk because if the if the math doesn't work we won't bid it out if that makes sense
We want to study it before we go out and do that. So I locked it on a contract to
December 31
But after that we're going to go we'll have to make a decision by December 30 30 31st to re-bid those
particular contracts and that's when they might raise it. Sure
More than lunch
More than likely we bid these out so it's we've already I think we've already executed the new term date with those
So those will terminate the
The can be been forwarded a council in such as it comes out so some may have some some opportunity for extended extending the contract
They have extensions available
But luckily ones tonight are very clear cut. I guess what I guess the ones of the bottom here are these the ones that are our streets
And we know we're doing a lot of streets and if we're on a risk of those being hired
And cost us more we will we will know before we make that decision
We've got two board members two council members that are a part of our subcommittee
And that's why we're taking the opportunity to really deep dive into these contracts before we take action
We did do some extensive discussion around this along with the
Jones
His name
Brad and myself had extensive conversations with him about that. So we're looking at all opportunities to see what our best report
Yeah, right right now with with John's information. This is our best deal in most flexibility
Please impact
Well, I know you do you guys will stay on top of it give us a form
For motion on these to prove
I'll make a motion
Yeah, okay
Hi
10 other new business of being which is residents of posting this agenda
11 staff reports
Pro trusty community announcements
13 adjourned motion
Second
High
Hi, I'm Parker.